Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor and Executive Vice President: David D. Henry and Carroll V. Newsom, John E. Ivey, Jr., George D. Stoddard, and Russell D. Niles 1942-1966 (Bulk 1952-1956) RG 6.0
New York University Archives
- Series II: John E. Ivey, Jr.
  - Subseries B: Admissions
    - Dean of Registration and Financial Aid, Office of, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Enrollment and Registration, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Registrar, Office of, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: All-University Departments
    - Annual Reports A-B, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports D-M, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports P-W, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Meetings of Department Heads, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254873
    - Policies and Procedures, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Professional School Cooperation, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Relationship of Commerce and Education, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Associations, Educational
    - American Association of University Professors, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - American Council on Education, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - National Commission on Accrediting, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Regional Systems (NEBE & WICHE), 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - New York State Educational Department, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Committees
    - Academic Advisory Council, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - College Qualification Center, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Computing Facilities, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Coordinated Language Study, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254881
    - Faculty Committee on Academic Personnel - Salary Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Geophysical Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Glen Ridge High School, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Provisional Admissions, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Registration Policies and Procedures, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Statistics, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Task Force Operations, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Task Force Operations, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Task Force Operations, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Television, All-University Committee on, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Tuition Evaluation, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Subseries F: Correspondence
    - Correspondence A-B, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence C-D, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence E-I, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence J-P, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254899
    - Correspondence Q, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence R, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence S-T, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence U-Z, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Subseries G: Deans
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science (Selection of New Dean), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science (Selection of New Dean), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Graduate School of Public Administration and Social Service, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - University College (Selection of New Dean), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Subseries H: Faculty
    - Commendations, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254907
    - University Senate, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Utilization, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Subseries I: Fundraising
    - Albert Gallatin Associates, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Federation, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Development, University, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ford Foundation, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Grants and Gifts, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Duplicates - Chancellor's Correspondence; A-Ae, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Duplicates - Chancellor's Correspondence; B-G, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Photographs separated from University Development, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Subseries J: Government, Federal
    - National Science Foundation, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254915
    - U.S. Office of Education, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subseries K: Heights Campus
    - Heights Campus, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Dormitory, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Technology Building #1, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Provost, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Subseries L: International Affairs
    - Brazilian Institute, 1953-1959 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Center for International Affairs (Trager), 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Center for International Affairs (Operation), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Center for International Affairs, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254923
    - Center for International Affairs, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Wallace Clark Center for International Management, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - International Conference of Scientific Information, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Institute for United Nations Study and Research (NYU and MSU), 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - International Seminar in Instructional TV and Radio, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Israel, 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Israel, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Powers, Phillip N., 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254931
    - SE Asia Regional Education Project and Nuclear Center, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Soviet-U.S. Engineering Exchange Program, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - GPASS (Program for Training Administrators), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Subseries M: Miscellaneous
    - Free European University, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - University Health Services, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - University Press, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Subseries L: Personnel
    - Personnel Division, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Prospective Personnel, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Subseries N: Schools
    - Athletics, Division of, 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Commerce, School of, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Commerce, School of, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254949
    - Dentistry, School of, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Education, School of, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Education, School of, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Engineering, School of, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Engineering, School of, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - General Division, Division of, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1956-1959 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254956
    - Graduate School of Public Administration and Social Service, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Graduate School of Public Administration and Social Service, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School of Public Administration and Social Service (Program), 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Graduate School of Public Administration and Social Service (Program), 1954-1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Law, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Medical Center, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254964
    - Medical Center, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - OSSBI (Office of Special Services to Business and Industry), 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - School of Retailing, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - University College of Arts and Science, 1956-1959 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Subseries O: Special Projects
    - Academy of Aeronautics, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Office of Applied Social Research Associates, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Archaeological Research, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Atomic Energy, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Bell Telephone Labs Program in Engineering, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Communication Arts Group, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254972
    - Continution Education Center, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Experimental Liberal Arts Program, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - French House, 19571958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Hall of American Studies, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Higher Education, Center for Study and Development of, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Institute for Industrial Behavior, 19571958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Learned Societies, 19581959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 19561958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - NEA-NYU Seminar - Creativity in American Culture, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Post-Doctoral Program in Psychology, 19551958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 19571959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Rehabilitation Services Center, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Rehabilitation Services Center, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Rehabilitation Services Center, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254980
    - Research, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Research, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Social Work Education (Pre-Professional Curriculum), 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Summer Theater Seminar and Workshop, University Heights, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Town Hall, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Subseries O: Students
    - Dean of Students, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Student Center, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Freshmen Orientation, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Gould Student Center, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Loeb Student Center, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Protestant Student Center, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Student Affairs, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Student Affairs, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Student Problems, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042254998
    - Student Problems, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Subseries P: Television, Educational
    - NYU College of the Air, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Progress Report on Educational Organization and Program, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Closed Circuit TV (Fund for Advancement of Education), 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Educational Television General File, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - College for Independent Study, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Educational Television Association (META), 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Series III: George D. Stoddard, 1960-1964
  George D. Stoddard's appointment by the Board of Trustees as Executive Vice-President took place on January 25, 1960 during the tenure of President Carroll V. Newsom (1956-1962). Stoddard had directed the exhaustive Self-Study, published in 1956, which redefined NYU's educational mission and constituency. He played a central role in constructing a new hierarchy of administrative offices that centralized educational policy and budgetary control, and in 1960 assumed the office he helped design, the second-highest at NYU.
  During Stoddard's tenure, the University expanded traditional instruction within the schools and fostered innovative programs in order to draw new students, such as the Communications Art Group and television instruction. The University experimented with international programs and cooperative education abroad while relationships with federal and state governments grew more diverse and complex. Stoddard associated himself with expansion of the Washington Square campus through renovation and construction, and several files in are concerned with space utilization and new construction. Wholly new programs appeared during his term of office, including recruitment and training for the Peace Corps and a new level of concern for on campus student health services. Of particular interest is Stoddards attention and response to preservation of the University's faculty, student, and operating records dating from 1962, the year in which major cities in the United States were being menaced by Russian missiles based in Cuba.
  Within the general correspondence files is correspondence regarding increasing levels of crime around the Height campus in 1959-1960 and its effect on faculty and students. Those files also contain restricted materials concerning a troubled student and a graduate whose credentials were questioned. The University College file contains a tentative policy statement of February 1960, regarding the education of women at the Heights campus. Stoddard's tenure spanned the period in which Newsom left office and James M. Hester became President.
  The records are arranged in four series that reflect the four years of his tenure, and each series is arranged alphabetically. The sub-headings are not uniform for all the series because new topical headings presented themselves as the office and its responsibilities elaborated the record-keeping system, and care must be exercised when searching for like files and like subjects within the four series. Some files appear to be incomplete, and the earliest files, some dating from 1957, date from prior administrations. This subgroup has been rearranged and refoldered by the supervising archivist, who discarded the folder dates because they were inaccurate and misleading. A few files are restricted that contain records of faculty discipline and tenure cases and an ROTC commission declination.
  - Subseries A: 1959-1961
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administration
      - Contract Officer, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255276
      - Voorhis, Harold O. - Vice-President and Secretary, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - University Development - Vice-President General Frank Howley, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - President, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Office of Institutional Research - J.D. Russell, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Office of Institutional Research - J.D. Russell, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Admissions and Registration
      - Registration and Financial Aid, Dean of - E.C. Kastner, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Admissions Office (F. Crossland), 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Admissions Office (F. Crossland), 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Registrar, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Sub-Subseries C: All-University Departments
      - Biology, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Chemistry, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Classics, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Economics, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - English, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Geology, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - German, 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Government, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255284
      - History, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Mathematics, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Music, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Philosophy, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Physics, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Psychology, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Romance Languages, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - All-University Department Heads - Senate Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Sociology, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Sub-Subseries D: Committees
      - Committee for Civilian Protection at Washington Square Center, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 11)
        3 1142 042255284
      - Membership and Donors, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Nursing Education, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Nursing Education, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Research Advisory Council, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Committee on Selective Service, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Sub-Subseries E: Foundations
      - Marshall Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Relm Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Subseries F: Government
      - ROTC, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - ROTC, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - State Education Department, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255292
      - State Education Department, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Sub-Subseries G: International Affairs
      - Hispanic-American Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Mediterranean Research Group, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Netherlands Summer Session, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Center for International Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Sub-Subseries H: Miscellaneous
      - University Representation at Miscellaneous Conferences, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Cooperative Education Study, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - International Education Exchange Program, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - New York University Glee Club, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Trimester Plan, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Sub-Subseries I: Schools
      - Athletics, Division of, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Commerce, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Dentistry, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Education, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Education, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Engineering, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        bar code: 3 1142 042255300
      - Division of General Education, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Graduate School of Social Work, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - La Maison Francaise, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Law, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Medicine, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Retailing, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - University College of Arts and Science, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Subseries J: Special Projects
      - Bard College, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Center for Applied Social Research, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Free Europe Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Office of Naval Research, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Patterson Moos Research, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - World Trade Center, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Dean of Students, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Sub-Subseries K: Television
      - Metropolitan Education Television Association (META), 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - All-University TV Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - RCA Workshop - Center for Instructional TV, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - RCA Workshop - Center for Instructional TV, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Sub-Subseries L: Undesignated
      - Dramatic Art (Washington Square), 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Undesignated Funds Form, 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Subseries B: 1960 - 1961
    - Administration - Ad Hoc Committee on Monthly Tuition, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255318
    - Administration - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Counseling, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Administration - Business Office, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Administration - Coordinator of Research Services (Sidney G. Roth), 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Administration - Office of Institutional Research, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Administration - University Relations (Arthur Brandon), 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Administration - Vice-President and Secretary (Harold O. Voorhis), 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Admission, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Coordinating Committee - Teaching of Liberal Arts and Sciences, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Foundations - Advancement of Education, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Government - International Cooperative and Administration, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Government - National Science Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Government - U. S. Office of Education, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Hofstra College, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - International - African Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255326
    - International - African Fair, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - International - African Scholarship Program, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - International - African Trip, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - International - Brazil Institute, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - International - Brazil Institute, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - International - Center for International Affairs, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - International - Institute for International Education, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - International - Israel Workshop, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - International - Spanish Institute, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - International - West Indies, University of, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Retirement - TIAA/CREF Retirement Plan, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Athletics, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255334
    - Schools - Commerce, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Communication Arts Group, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Art Education Department, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Schools - General Education, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Schools - Law, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      bar code: 3 1142 042255342
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Mathematical Sciences, Institute of, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Medical College, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Schools - University College, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Washington Square College, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Space - Stoddard Horner Group, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Space - Task Force on Space, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Space - Washington Square Committee, Space Allocation, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 11)